<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>evad.lol</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on evad.lol</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.125.4</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 17:34:41 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Media</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pages/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 17:34:41 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pages/media/</guid>
      <description>Only adding media worth spending time with. I started the Media section in May so it&amp;rsquo;s incomplete, but I&amp;rsquo;ll do my best to add things as they&amp;rsquo;re remembered.
Reading in 2024 Killing Commendatore (2017) by Haruki Murakami – Reread
Chenneville (2023) by Paulette Jiles
Martyr! (2024) by Kaveh Akbar
The Saint of Bright Doors (2023) by Vajra Chandrasekera
Children of Ruin (2019) by Adrian Tchaikovsky
When We Cease to Understand the World (2020) by Benjamín Labatut</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Me?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:09:07 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been designing and developing digital products and entertainment experiences for nearly (omg) three decades.
What I love is leading and collaborating with highly intelligent designers and partners, all of us obsessed with creating an outstanding customer experience.
Throughout my career, I’ve had the privilege of working on an amazing range of fascinating projects alongside many remarkable teams and individuals. Looking back, I can see how these diverse and often challenging efforts have profoundly shaped my professional development.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ear Demands Some Variety</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-ear-demands-some-variety/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 11:57:19 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-ear-demands-some-variety/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t recall where I first ran across this sound advice, but I&amp;rsquo;ve referred to it many times over the years.
Transcribed thanks to GPT-4-Vision. 😉
“This sentence has five words. Here are five more words. Five-word sentences are fine. But several together are monotonous. Listen to what is happening. The writing is getting boring. The sound of it drones. It’s like a stuck record. The ear demands some variety.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s on My Desk 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-my-desk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:57:19 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/whats-on-my-desk/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve arguably spent way too much time tweaking and futzing my home office setup. Here&amp;rsquo;s where I&amp;rsquo;m at.
Desk
30” x 60” Javis Powdercoated Standing Desk in black by Fully. I don’t think they make this particular model anymore but it’s perfect for me, especially after adding big, rubbery wheels for rolling on and not destroying our hardwood floors.
Chair
A classic Herman Miller Aeron Chair which I’ve had for nearly 20 years.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
